Guide to the the Richard W. Lyman, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0215
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Papers, Series 1
  - Buck Club Grants-In-Aid, 1955-62 (Box 53, Folder 43)
  - Grants-in-Aid, Dean of Students Fund, 1940-62 (Box 53, Folder 44)
  - Engineering Student Aid Fund, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 45)
  - Law School. Grant-in-Aid, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 46)
  - Susan Leighton Memorial Fund, 1938-50 (Box 53, Folder 47)
  - Grants-in-Aid, Student Aid Fund (various donors), 1937-62 (Box 53, Folder 48)
  - Religious Activities. Includes the following 11 envelopes: (Box 53, Folder 49)
  - Brandeis University (Box 53, Folder 49.1)
  - Princeton University (Box 53, Folder 49.1)
  - Queen's University (Box 53, Folder 49.11)
  - University of Chicago (Box 53, Folder 49.2)
  - Columbia University (Box 53, Folder 49.3)
  - Cornell University (Box 53, Folder 49.4)
  - Dartmouth College (Box 53, Folder 49.5)
  - Duke University (Box 53, Folder 49.6)
  - University of Michigan (Box 53, Folder 49.7)
  - Northwestern University (Box 53, Folder 49.8)
  - Pennsylvania State (Box 53, Folder 49.9)
  - LASSU REPORT of Religious Activities (and background material), 1963 (Box 53, Folder 50)
  - Board of Trustees (file #1), 1970-71; B1 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees, misc, 1971-72; B1 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Gardner Committee: Study of Board of Trustee Structure, B10.2 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees meetings schedule, 1970-72; B13 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Students on Trustee committees, 1970-71; B14.2.3 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, Board of Trustees, 1970-72; B14.3 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Finance and Development Committee, Board of Trustees, 1971-72; B14.4 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Investment Committee, Board of Trustees, 1972; B14.5 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Investment Committee, Board of Trustees, 1971-72; B14.5 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Board of Trustees, Committee on Investment Responsibility, 1970-71; B14.5 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Land and Building, Board of Trustees, 1970-72; B14.6 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Nominations, Board of Trustees, 1965-72; B14.7 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Sub-committee charged with identifying potential additional women trustees, 1971; B14.7 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Religion, 1965-72; AD2.24 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - On-campus and military recruiting, 1971-72; AD2.3 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Stanford mascot/symbol, file #1. [out - file transferred to SC215 Series 3 Box 44], 1972; AD2.7 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Stanford mascot/symbol, file #2. [out - file transferred to SC 215 Box 44 - 6/2010 not found, search in process], 1970-72; AD2 7 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Conscientious objection, 1970-71; AD2.9 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Free speech issue, 1968-71; AD2.12 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Homosexuality, 1971; AD2.13 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Honorarium, 1970; AD2.14 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Pre-election recess-"Princeton plan", 1970-72; AD2.23 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - ROTC-Navy, l970-72; AD2.26 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - ROTC-Army, 1970-72; AD2.26 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - ROTC, January 1971-August 1972; AD2.26 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - ROTC, 1970-72; AD2.26 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - ROTC, June-Sept. 1970; AD2.26 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Speeches, other than R.W. Lyman's, 1969-71; AD3.22 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Lyman interviews/remarks/statements on issues, 1970-72; AD3.22 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Speech materials, 1967-69; AD3.22 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - President's Office, l970-72; AD4 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - President's Schedule, 1971-72; AD4.9 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Presidential Staff Meetings, 1970-72; AD4.11 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Vice presidential group, 1972; AD4.12 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Past Presidents, 1970; AD4.13 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Condolence letters; deceased letters, 1970-72; AD4.20.2 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Congratulations, 1971-72; AD4.20.3 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Invitations, 1970-72; AD4.20.4 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Troubled: Pearlstein, Carl, 1964-1972; AD4.20.5 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Complaints; nonsense letters, AD4.20.5 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Complaints II (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Complaints III (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Recommendations, routine, 1970-72; AD4.20.6 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Complaints I (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Ombudsman, 1970-72; AD6 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Campus disruptions and demonstrations, 1968-71; AD7.2 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Student discipline, Board of Trustees, 1963-72; AD7.2.3/1 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Judicial Council (SJC), Case # file, 1969-71; AD7.2.7 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Judicial Council (SJC), 1970-72; AD7.2.7 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Fraud, 1971; AD7.7 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Judicial systems, 1972; AD7.9.1 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Legal cases, 1970-71; AD7.10 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Admissions Office, 1970-72; AD8.1 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Admissions, Student cases, file #1, 1971-72; AD8.1.2 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Admissions, student cases, file #2, 1971-72; AD8.1.2 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Dean of Student affairs, 1970-72; AD8.8 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Discrimination policy, [1969?]; AD8.8.3 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Drug use, 1970-71; AD8.9 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Exchange programs, 1970-71; AD8.10 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Overseas campuses, misc, 1970-72; AD8.11 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Financial aids, 1970-71; AD8.12 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Student loans, professional school loan bank, 1970-71; AD8.12.1 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Guide Service, 1971; AD8.15 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Housing Office, misc. reports, 1970-72; AD8.18.1 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Columbae House, AD8.18.6/1 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Fraternities, 1970-71; AD8.18.8 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Housing for students, 1970-72 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Social regulations, 1967-70; AD8.18.15 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - I.D. cards, 1970-71; AD8.19 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Women at Stanford, 1970-72; AD9.5 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Affirmative Action program, 1972; AD9.6 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Affirmative Action program, internal, 1970-72; AD9.6 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - [various affirmative action reports] (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Affirmative Action for women. file #1, 1970-71; AD9.6.3 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Affirmative Action for women. file #2, 1971-72; AD9.6.3 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Personnel and employee relations, 1970-72; AD10 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Employment inquiries and requests, 1970-72; AD10.1 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Staff development programs, 1970-72; AD10.2 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Administrative searches, [Retrieved by President's Office 5/01/79], 1971-72; AD10.3 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Administrative appointments, 1969-72; AD10.4 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Policy: appointment of lecturers and other short-term teachers, l969-72; AD10.6 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Employee organizations, 1970-71; AD10.7 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous ad hoc employee organizations, 1971; AD10.7.1 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Stanford chapter. of the California School employees Assoc, 1972; AD10.7 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Stanford Credit Union, 1967-71; AD10.7.3 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Committee for Art, 1970-72; AD10.7.4 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Day Care Center, 1969-72; AD10.7.5 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - United Stanford employees, 1970-73; AD10.7.8 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Distaff Club, 1970-72; AD10.7.6 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Stanford Employees Assoc, 1970-72; AD10.7.7 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Personnel policies, 1971-72; AD10.8 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Collective bargaining, 1970-72; AD10.8.2 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Labor relations policy group, 1970-71; AD10.8.2/1 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Minority Employment and recruitment, 1970-71; AD10.8.4 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Staff fringe benefits, 1970-72; AD10.8.9 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Part-time staff: policy re:, 1971; AD10.8.9/1 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Policy: benefits for visiting scholars, fellow, 1972; AD10.8.9/2 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Grievance hearings/cases, 1971-72; AD10.8.10/1 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Graduate students (employed) grievance procedures, 1970-72; AD10.8.10/2 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Grievances: student/faculty on academic matters, 1972; AD10.8.10/3 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Health insurance, 1971-72; AD10.8.11 (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - Hiring practices, 1970-72; AD10.8.12 (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - Leaves of absence, 1970-72; AD10.8.15 (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - Retirement/annuity programs (Prudential and TIAA-CREF), l966?-1972; AD10.8.17 (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - Salaries, 1970-72; AD10.8.19 (Box 58, Folder 29)
  - Policy: Travel / vacations, 1970-72; AD10.8.21 (Box 58, Folder 30)
  - Tuition benefit plan, 1970-72; AD10.8.22 (Box 58, Folder 31)
  - Jury duty, 1962-72; AD10.8.26 (Box 58, Folder 32)
  - University Services, misc, 1972; AD.11 (Box 58, Folder 33)
  - Fire department, 1971-72; AD11.2 (Box 58, Folder 34)
  - Food Service, 1970-71; AD11.3 (Box 58, Folder 35)
  - Vending machines/vending/vendors, 1970-72; AD11.3.1 (Box 58, Folder 36)
  - Plant Services, 1967-72; AD11.4 (Box 58, Folder 37)
  - Police services, 1968-72; AD11.6 (Box 58, Folder 38)
  - Police and campus security, 1970-72; AD11.6.2 (Box 58, Folder 39)
  - Arson and possible arson cases/fires, 1971-72; AD11.6.2/1 (Box 58, Folder 40)
  - Crime and crime prevention, 1970-72; AD11.6.2/4 (Box 58, Folder 41)
  - Vandalism, 1970-72; AD11.6.2/5 (Box 58, Folder 42)
  - Policy: weapons on campus, 1970-71; AD11.6.2/6 (Box 58, Folder 43)
  - Vehicle regulations, 1972; AD11.6.5 (Box 58, Folder 44)
  - Office of public events, 1970-72; AD11.7 (Box 58, Folder 45)
  - University ceremonies, annual programs, misc, 1970; AD11.7.1 (Box 58, Folder 46)
  - Commencement at other universities, 1971; AD11.7.2/1 (Box 58, Folder 47)
  - Freshman convocation, 1971; AD11.7.3 (Box 58, Folder 48)
  - Freshman convocation, 1970; AD11.7.3 (Box 58, Folder 49)
  - Pre-registration program, 1970; AD11.7.12 (Box 58, Folder 50)
  - Summer festivals, 1971; AD11.7.13 (Box 58, Folder 51)
  - Publications service/communications, 1970-72; AD11.8 (Box 58, Folder 52)
  - Microfilm records, 1970-71; AD11.8.3 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Stanford News Service, 1970-72; AD11.8.4 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - News Service reports/releases, 1970-72; AD11.8.5 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Questionnaires/questions, 1970-72; AD11.8.10 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Stanford publications, misc, 1970-72; AD11.8.11 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Opinion polls, 1971; AD11.8.7 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Mothers Club of Stanford Univ, 1970-72; AD11.9.1 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Financial management of the University, 1971; AD12 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Business and finance, 1971-72; AD12.2 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Administrative data processing, 1970-71; AD12.3 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Budgets, 1971-72; AD12.5 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Budgets, file#1, 11/70-5/71; AD12.5 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Federal input for budget, 1969-70; AD12.5.2 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Room and board rates, 1971-72; AD12.5.3 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Tuition, Stanford, 1970-72; AD12.5.4 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Wage and price freeze issue, 1971-72; AD12.5.5 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Financial reports, 1971-72; AD12.6 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Consultants, 1970-72; AD12.7.1 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Insurance, risk management, 1970-72; AD12.8 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Taxes, tax data, 1970-72; AD12.9 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - General Secretary's Office, 1970-72; AD12.10.1 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Endowment, Stanford, 1970-72; AD12.10.2 (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Fund raising, 1970-72; AD12.10.3 (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - Estates and wills, l970[?]-72; AD12.10.3/3 (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - Stanford Annual Fund (Inner Quad), 1970-72; AD12.10.3/4 (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - Gift Policies: Gift summaries, 1970-71; AD12.10.3/5 (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - United Fund campaign/Community Fund/CHAD, 1970-72; AD12.10.8 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Patent administration, 1969-71; AD12.11 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Planning, long range estimates, 1971-72; AD12.12 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Resources for the future, 1970-72; AD12.12.1 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Surveys and studies, misc, 1970-72; AD12.12.2 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Land and buildings, 1952-72; AD12.14 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Policy: use of land and facilities, 1954-72; AD12.14.1 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Club (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Visitors, 1971-72; AD13.10 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Guest-in-residence program, 1970; AD13.10.2 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Foreign visitors, 1971-72; AD13.10.3 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Speakers on campus, 1970-72; AD13.10.4 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Visiting committees, 1969-72; AD13.10.5 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Visiting committee, general file,'71, [1970-72]; AD13.10.5 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Trustee participation in visiting committees, 1971; AD13.10.5 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Advisory committee, Computer Science. [File checked out 2/13/79], 1970-72; AD13.10.5/1 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Advisory committee, Computer Science. [File checked out 2/13/79], 1967-72; AD13.10.5/1 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Visiting committee (advisory) Earth Sciences, l971-72; AD13.10.5/2 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Earth Sciences, Advisory Board, 1961-72; AD13.10.5/2 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - SED subcommittee on higher education, 1963; AD13.10.5/3 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Education visiting committee, 1961-71; AD13.10.5/3 (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Visiting committee, international studies, 1970-71; AD13.10.5/4 (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Law School Board of Visitors, 1970-72; AD13.10.5/5 (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Law School Board of Visitors, 1961-1972; AD13.10.5/5 (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Members, Law School Board of Visitors, 1962-68; AD13.10.5/5 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - School of Medicine Visiting Committee, 1971-72; AD13.10.5/6 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - School of Medicine Visiting Committee, 1965-72; AD13.10.5/6 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Engineering Visiting Committee, 1971-72; AD13.10.5/7 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Engineering Advisory Council, 1966(?)-71; AD13.10.5/7 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Graduate School of Business Advisory Council, 1970-71; AD13.10.5/8 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Business School Advisory Council, 1968-71; AD13.10.5/8 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Graduate School of Business Advisory Council, Reports, 1959-71; AD13.10.5/8(?) (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Graduate School of Business Advisory Council members, 1958-68; AD13.10.5/8(?) (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Library Visiting Committee, 1971-72; AD13.10.5/9 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Library Visiting Committee proposal, 1971-72; AD13.10.5/9 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Hopkins Marine Station Advisory Committee, AD13.10.5/11 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Hopkins Marine Station Advisory Committee, 1967-72; AD13.10.5/11 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Provost's Office, 1971-72; AA1 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Provost's staff minutes, 1970-72; AA1.4 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Deans' Council correspondence, 1971-72; AA1.5 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Academic Information Center, 1970-71; AA1.6 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Academic Planning Office, 1969-72; AA1.7 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Dean of the Chapel, 1971-72; AA1.8 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - United Campus Christian Ministry, 1970-71; AA1.10 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Officer of Undergraduate Studies, 1970-72; AA1.12 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Tutoring program, 1972; AA1.12.1 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Urban studies, 1970-72; AA1.12.2 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Graduate division, 1970-72; AA1.13 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Terman Faculty Planning Study, 1970; AA2.1.2/1 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Emeriti, 1971; AA2.2 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Faculty appointments, 1970-72; AA2.3 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Academic freedom, 1966-71; AA2.6.1 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Dissenting faculty; disruptions, 1970-72; AA2.6.2 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper clippings, press releases, etc. re: the Franklin case, AA2.6.2/1 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Letters re: Franklin issue, A-G, AA2.6.2/1 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Letters re: Franklin issue, H-O, AA2.6.2/1 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Letters re: Franklin issue, P-Z, AA2.6.2/1 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Faculty self-discipline, 1970-72; AA2.6.3 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - American Assoc. of University Professors (AAUP), Report on faculty self-discipline (Packer committee), 1970-71; AA2.6.3/1 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Teaching load policy, 1972; AA2.6.8 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Tenure: policy, 1967-72; AA2.6/9 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - AAUP, Stanford chapter, 1970-72; AA2.8 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Fellows of the University, 1969-72; AA2.9 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Research and teaching assistants, 1969-72; AA2.11 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Voluntary faculty groups, 1971; AA2.13 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Faculty political action group (FPAG), 1970-72; AA2.13.2 (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - SLAC-Physics relations, 1963-73 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - File memos re: Physics Dept.-SLAC [in orange binder] (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - copies of memos, reports, letters, etc. re: SLAC or physics dept. [filed loose, not in a file folder] (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Univ. national rating/accreditation, 1969-71; AA.3.4 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Advising, counseling and testing, 1970-72; AA3.7 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Pre-medical advising, 1970-71; AA3.7.1 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Course credit issues, 1967-72; AA3.8 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Course evaluation, 1969-72; AA3.8.1 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Curriculum, 1962-72; AA3.9 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Degrees/honorary degrees, 1970-72; AA3.10 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Educational innovations, 1970-72; AA3.11 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Stanford and U.C. exchange programs, 1964-72; AA3.12 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - On campus seminars, symposia, etc, 1971; AA3.15 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Summer sessions, 1970-72; AA3.16 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Freshman seminars, 1970-72; AA3.18.1 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Study of Education at Stanford, 1969-72; AA3.19 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - School of Humanities and Sciences, 1965-71; AA4.1 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Afro-American studies, 1971; AA4.1.4 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Art and Architecture, 1970-72; AA4.1.9 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Applied Physics, visiting committee, 1971-72; AA4.1.8 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Communications, 1970-72; AA4.1.15 (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Drama, 1971-72; AA4.1.18 (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - English, 1971-72; AA4.1.21 (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - French and Italian Dept, 1971-72; AA4.1.22 (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - German, 1971-72; AA4.1.24 (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - History, 1970-71; AA4.1.25 (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Human biology, 1969-71; AA4.1.26 (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - Mathematics, 1969-71; AA4.1.27 (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - Music, 1971-72; AA4.1.29 (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - Physical Education and athletics, 1970-71; AA4.1.30 (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Physical Education and athletics, 1965-70; AA4.1.30 (Box 63, Folder 31)
  - P. E. and athletics, 1971-72; AA4.1.30 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Football, 1970; AA4.1.30/1 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Big Game (away), 1970; AA4.1.30/1 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Rose bowl expenses, 1971-72; AA4.1.30/2 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Rose bowl game, 1971-72; AA4.1.30/2 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Rose bowl game, January 1, 1971; AA4.l.30/2 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Rose bowl game; Physical education and athletics, (1970-71); AA4.1.30/2 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Rose bowl trip, RWL -ESL, 1970-72; AA4.1.30/2 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Athletic Board, P.E. and athletics, 1971-72; AA4.1.30/3 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Athletic Board, P.E. and athletics, 1970-71; AA4.1.30/3 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Athletic Board, P.E. and athletics, 1964-72; AA4.1.30/3 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Women's physical education, 1971-72; AA4.1.31 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Physics, 1971; AA4.1.33 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Political Science, 1970-71; AA4.1.34 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Psychology, 1970-72; AA4.1.35 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Social Sciences (special program), 1972; AA4.1.39 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Sociology, 1972; AA4.1.40 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Spanish and Portuguese, 1970-72; AA4.1.41 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Statistics (miscellaneous), 1969-71; AA4.1.42 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Black studies institute, 1971; AA4.1.43 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Chicano studies institute, 1969-71; AA4.1.44 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Chicano studies program, 1971; AA4.1.44/1 (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Graduate School of Business, 1969-72; AA4.2 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - School of Earth Sciences, 1970-72; AA4.3 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - School of Engineering, 1970-72; AA4.4 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Electrical Engineering, 1970-72; AA4.4.5 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Industrial Engineering, 1970-73; AA4.4.6 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Center for Materials Research, 1970-72; AA4.4.7 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Materials Science Engineering, 1968-70; AA4.4.8 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - School of Education, 1970-72; AA4.5 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Medical School, July-August 1972; AA4.6 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Medical School, January-June 1972; AA4.6 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Medical School, July-December 1971; AA4.6 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - School of Medicine, January-June 1971; AA4.6 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - School of Medicine, up to December 1970; AA4.6 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Patient care center, 1970-71; AA4.6.2 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Medical School Executive Committee (correspondence), 1971; AA4.6.3 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Medical School Executive Committee (correspondence), January-August 1972; AA4.6 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Medical Service Plan, 1971; AA4.6.4 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Nursing program, 1970-72; AA4.6.5 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Food Research Institute, 1971; AA4.8 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Hoover Institute, 1969-72; AA4.9 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Hoover Institution, 1969; AA4.9 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Hoover Institution, 1970; AA4.9 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Hoover Institution, Board of Overseers, 1971; AA4.9.1 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - International Studies, Center for Research in, 1971; AA4.10 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - International Studies, visiting committee, 1968; AA.4.10 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Center for Latin American studies, 1969-72; AA4.11 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Libraries, 1970-72; AA4.12 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - SLAC (Stanford Linear Accelerator Center), File #1, 1970-71; AA4.13 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Public Law Advocates, Stanford, 1971; AA4.15.1 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Computation Center, 1967-72; AA4.16 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Stanford University Hospital, 1968-72; AA4.17 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Stanford University Hospital, general members, 1969-72; AA4.17.1 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Stanford University Hospital Board of Directors, 1968-71; AA4.17.2 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Stanford Hospital disruptions, 1971; AA4.17.3 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Awards and Prizes, misc, 1923-72; AA5 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Dean's List, 1967-71; AA5.1 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1970-72; AA5.2 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - White House Fellows, 1964-72; AA5.4 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Ernest C. Arbuckle Award, 1968-71; AA5.7 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Jake Gimbel Athletic Attitude Prize, 1959-72; AA5.24 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Graves Awards, 1967-71; AA5.28 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Royal Society of Arts, 1971; AA5.48 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Grants, misc, 1970-72; AA6 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Special Tuition Grants Fund, 1971; AA.6.1 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Scholarships, misc, 1943-72; AA7 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Scholarships at other institutions, 1971-72; AA7.1 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - California State Scholarship Fund, 1970-72; AA7.2 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Canfield Scholarships, 1970-72; AA7.3 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Cap and Gown Scholarship, 1970-72; AA7.4 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - A.P. Giannini Scholarship Foundation, 1970-72; AA7.9 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Heritage Fund, 1970-72; AA7.11 (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - Proctor and Gamble Scholarship, 1970; AA7.20 (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Mabel Wilson Richards Scholarship Fund, 1970-72; AA7.22 (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - Sloss, Leon Jr. Memorial Lectures, 1971; AA7.26 (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - Board of Trustees Scholarship, 1968; AA7.31 (Box 67, Folder 22)
  - Alice C. Woodbury Scholarship, 1969-71; AA7.33 (Box 67, Folder 23)
  - Fellowships, Misc. / general, AA8 (Box 67, Folder 24)
  - Fellowships, Honorary, 1941-64; AA8.2 (Box 67, Folder 25)
  - Fellowships, Honorary, 1956-73; AA8.2 (Box 67, Folder 26)